final Map<String, Map<String, List<Map<String, dynamic>>>> engQuestions = {


  'Engineering': {
    'AutoCAD': [
      {
        'question': 'What is the purpose of layers in AutoCAD?',
        'options': ['Coloring', 'Managing drawing components', 'Zooming', 'Exploding'],
        'answer': 'Managing drawing components',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which command is used to offset objects?',
        'options': ['LINE', 'OFFSET', 'COPY', 'MOVE'],
        'answer': 'OFFSET',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which file extension does AutoCAD use?',
        'options': ['.cad', '.dwg', '.ai', '.pdf'],
        'answer': '.dwg',
      },
    ],
    'MATLAB': [
      {
        'question': 'What does "plot(x, y)" do in MATLAB?',
        'options': ['Opens figure', 'Creates a 2D graph', 'Saves file', 'Clears workspace'],
        'answer': 'Creates a 2D graph',
      },
      {
        'question': 'What is a "script" in MATLAB?',
        'options': ['A chart', 'A set of commands saved in a file', 'UI component', 'Toolbox'],
        'answer': 'A set of commands saved in a file',
      },
      {
        'question': 'How to define a matrix?',
        'options': ['{1,2}', '(1 2)', '[1 2; 3 4]', '"1,2"'],
        'answer': '[1 2; 3 4]',
      },
    ],
    'Embedded Systems': [
      {
        'question': 'Embedded systems are usually:',
        'options': ['General-purpose computers', 'Part of larger devices', 'Cloud servers', 'Databases'],
        'answer': 'Part of larger devices',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Microcontrollers are often used in:',
        'options': ['Video games', 'Embedded systems', 'Social media', 'Databases'],
        'answer': 'Embedded systems',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which language is mostly used in embedded systems?',
        'options': ['Python', 'Java', 'C', 'SQL'],
        'answer': 'C',
      },
    ],
    'Robotics': [
      {
        'question': 'What is the main component to control robot motion?',
        'options': ['Sensor', 'Actuator', 'Battery', 'CPU'],
        'answer': 'Actuator',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Robots perceive the environment using:',
        'options': ['Microphones', 'Sensors', 'Hands', 'Batteries'],
        'answer': 'Sensors',
      },
      {
        'question': 'Which field combines AI with robotics?',
        'options': ['Mechatronics', 'Neuroscience', 'Automation', 'Robotic Vision'],
        'answer': 'Robotic Vision',
      },
    ],
  }, };